emeraldescape.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy- Luxco

This is the privacy policy of Luxco’s Web site www.luxco.com, which shall include, without limitation, the home page, splash page, and all other pages under the same top level domain name, and all content thereon (the "Site") as provided by the Luxco, ("Luxco" or "we").

**Collecting Information:**  
Personally Identifiable Information

This Site requests and collects certain personally identifiable information such as name, address, phone number and e-mail address through various means, such as Site registration, surveys, games, questions, comments and communications to the Site, and postings to chat and bulletin areas, if any.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information at our Site, such as annual income, buying preferences, or age, also known as demographic or profile data, though this information is optional.

**Cookies:**  
"Cookies" are pieces of information that are placed on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Site. We may use cookies to customize your experience on the Site. We may also use cookies to record how many times a user has visited our Site and what pages the user has accessed. You may, however, disallow receiving cookies at any time through your web browser. It is not our intention to use cookies to retrieve information that is unrelated to our Site or your interaction with our Site.

**IP Address**  
We may collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. This information does not contain any personally identifiable information about you. Your IP address is also used to help identify you during a particular session and to gather broad demographic data.

**Usage:**  
Luxco and its affiliates use information collected on and through this Site to comply with the purpose for which such information was collected and other purposes, as disclosed at the time such information is provided, or as described in this policy. For example, the information collected on and through the Site may be used to send you information about our and our affiliates' products and services and updates to our Site. In certain instances you will have an opportunity to limit this use at time the information is collected. You also may limit this use by following the instructions in Choice/Opt-out below. We may use the information we gather along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties.

With respect to non-personally identifiable information, we may use this data to improve our Site and to send you information that may be of interest to you. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising on the Site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person. This information may also be used to evaluate what portions of the Site are more popular than others, determine where visitors came from, and where they go, and how long visitors stay on a particular page, or the Site in general.

**Sharing:**  
Luxco may share your personally identifiable information with business partners that we believe may provide offers that may be of interest to you. In certain instances you will have an opportunity to limit this sharing at the time the information is collected. You also may limit this sharing by following the instructions in Choice/Opt-out below.

Certain services available on the Site may be provided by third parties. For example, if you choose to purchase products or services from the Site, the information you provide in connection with such purchase may be used by an authorized vendor to fulfill that order. Your provision of information to these third parties will be governed by the privacy practices of that third party; please check for the privacy policy link on the page on which you are requested to provide information.

In order to make the Site more enjoyable for visitors, Luxco constantly strives to learn how users use the Site. Information concerning your use of the Site and related services may be made available to one or more third parties, such as a data processor, fulfillment agency, or advertising agency, for these purposes.

Luxco may transfer, sell or assign information concerning your use of this Site, including without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your use of the Site, to third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of Luxco.

Luxco may make information concerning users of the Site available to law enforcement personnel and agencies when requested to do so or as required by law.  
**  
Posting Information on or Through the Site:**  
You are solely responsible for the information and other content you post on or through the Site. See Terms and Conditions. You understand that personal and other information (e.g., user name, e-mail address, phone number) that you post on or through the Site (e.g., chat, bulletin boards, post cards, invitations), is generally accessible to and may be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others. Users of these forums are encouraged to exercise caution when providing personal information about themselves.

**Security:**  
We take security very seriously. We provide for the secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers by using encryption software. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and us, and us and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.

**Consent to Processing:**  
By providing any personal information to this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of such personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in, the United States and other countries or territories.

**Links:**  
This Site may contain links or references to other Web sites outside of our control. Please be aware that we have no control over these sites and our privacy policy does not apply to these sites.

**Access:**  
If you would like to review and/or update the information that you have provided to the Site, please send an e-mail to margaritavilletequila@qualitycustomercare.com requesting such access or change.

**Choice/Opt-out:**  
You may choose to have your name taken off of Luxco's e-mail list or have Luxco not provide your information to others in the future by (1) sending an e-mail to unsubscribe@luxco.com with the subject line "Unsubscribe to Luxco" or "Unsubscribe to Partners," or by (2) following instructions as provided in any e-mail message from Luxco.

**Use of Site**  
The Site may only be used or otherwise accessed by you if you are of legal age to purchase beverage alcohol in the jurisdiction in which you reside. See Terms and Conditions. If we receive notice, or reasonably believe, that someone under legal purchasing age has provided us with personal information, we will make reasonable efforts to remove such personal information from our database.

**Your Acceptance of this Policy:**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

Luxco  
5050 Kemper Avenue  
St. Louis, Missouri 63139, U.S.A.
